Guide to Tuli Kupferberg and Sylvia Topp Papers MSS.385
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VII. Publications, 1942-2008, undated; 55 Linear Feet in 25 manuscript boxes, 3 flat boxes, and 25 oversize boxes
  - Smoke Signals, Soho Weekly News, 1984, 1974-1976 (Box 281, Folder 1-4)
  - Soho Weekly News, 1976-1979 (Box 282, Folder 1-4)
  - Soho News, Sounds - Street News, 1980, 1982, 1985, 1997-1998 (Box 283, Folder 1-3)
  - Street News, 2000-2007 (Box 284, Folder 1-3)
  - Stony Hills - The Village Voice, 1966-1994, 2003, undated (Box 285, Folder 1-5)
  - The Village Voice, 1978-1988 (Box 286, Folder 1-3)
  - The Village Voice, 1995-1997, 2002-2003 (Box 287, Folder 1-3)
  - The Village Voice - The Weekly Westport Trucker, 1967-1973, 2004-2009 (Box 288, Folder 1-3)
  - The Westsider - Yipster Times, 1967-2004 (Box 289, Folder 1-5)
- Series VIII. Correspondence, 1949-2010, undated; 9 Linear Feet in 9 record cartons; 1.4 Megabytes
  Folders were arranged alphabetically by sender's last name, company name, or subject title. Archivist-arranged general correspondence files were grouped by decade following the individual files. Some correspondents within the general files may also have individual files within this series.
  This series contains letters from friends and colleagues, many who were notable political figures, artists, writers involved in the arts scene in New York and internationally during the 1960s through 1990s, including Sam Abrams, Al Aronowitz, Coby Batty, Lenni Brenner, Noam Chomsky, Diane di Prima, Royston Ellis, Lawrence Ferlinghetti, Allen Ginsberg, Urban Gwerder, Harry Hooton, Ted Joans, LeRoi Jones, Walter Lowenfels, Arthur Moyse, Anais Nin, Genesis P-Orridge, Sparrow, Ed Sanders, Rebby Sharp, Robin Tatham, Allen Tobias, and Judith Wehlau. This series also contains writing and music samples from admirers as well as reader responses and suggestions to Kupferberg's works. A significant section of the series contains general correspondence in paper and electronic records, grouped by decade, received from friends, fans, and publishers. This series also contains fan mail for his band The Fugs and for Kupferberg himself. The largest portion of the fan mail dates from the 1960s and documents the thoughts, issues, and activities of young people during the 1960s, living in the United States, as well as internationally. Kupferberg appears to have responded regularly to these fan letters. Also of note in this series are responses and reader suggestions regarding Kupferberg's Dope Lore column, which ran through the early 1980s and was primarily about drug use. The letters within this series are mostly those received by Kupferberg, except for a few folders specifically noted as written by him, and a few of his notes and responses scattered throughout the files. This series also includes a small amount of limited-circulation publications, usually attached to letters from publishers with whom Kupferberg exchanged his own publications. Correspondence regarding Birth Press can be found in Series V.
  - 75th Birthday Letters For Kupferberg, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Abrams, Cory, 1997-2004 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Abrams, Sam, 2006-2008 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Am Here Books, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Anti-Olympics, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Aronowitz, Al, 1992-1995 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - As They Were Rejection Letters, 1992-1993 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Auschwitz-Hiroshima Quote, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Bach, John, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Batty, Coby, 1999-2007 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Bellondi, Vincent, 1965-1966 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Berge, Carol, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Berke, Joe, 1969-1973 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Berrigan, Ted (Includes Photographs), 1974 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Birds Do It-Related, 1969-1970 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Boardman, John, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Body Language (Re: Chapter Four), 1975 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Bowles, Paul, 1962 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Bracken, Len, 1994-1995 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Brenner, Lenni (Includes Brenner Articles), 1993-1998 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Brill's Content Magazine, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Broadway, Brooke (Includes Jack Kerouac Recommendation Letter), 1960-1961 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Brooklyn College, 1989-1990 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Brown, Rob, 2008 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Bruce (Bypass Publication), 1995 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Bukowski, Charles (Submission?), circa 1958-1964 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Cards (Greeting), 1975-2009 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Carnival Knowledge Publication, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Chaffey, Ed "Buzz", 1989, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - Charters, Anne, 1987, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - Chomsky, Noam, 2004-2008 (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - Circumcision (Re: Sylvia Topp Article), 1968-1985 (Box 41, Folder 32-34)
  - Circumcision (New York Times Letter to the Editor), 1998 (Box 41, Folder 35)
  - Club Vanity/Vanity Press, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 36)
  - Cockburn, Alexander, 1991-2008 (Box 41, Folder 37)
  - Contact/mailing lists, 2001, undated (Box 41, Folder 38)
  - Crawdaddy Form Letter, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 39)
  - Crazy Paper (Fan Mail), 1977-1982 (Box 41, Folder 40)
  - Cuba (Music Festival), 1967 (Box 41, Folder 41)
  - Dara, undated (Box 41, Folder 42)
  - David Susskind Show, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 43)
  - Dean, Ann (Flower Power Publication), 1993 (Box 41, Folder 44)
  - Deathrage, Karen (Re: Poem), 1989 (Box 41, Folder 45)
  - Demon Records, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 46)
  - di Prima, Diane, 1968, 2002-2004 (Box 41, Folder 47)
  - Dixie Parasong and Blue Horse Publications, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 48)
  - The Door, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 49)
  - Dope Lore Submissions, 1980-1984 (Box 41, Folder 50-54)
  - Drafts, Letters By Kupferberg, 1961-2008 (Box 42, Folder 1-2)
  - Drooker, Eric, 1986-2007 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Drove Old Dixie Down (Re: Song Used for Movie The Last Waltz), 1978 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Duhon, Eliot, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - E-Sales (Re: The Fugs and Kupferberg Memorabilia, Sketches, Etc.), 1999-2001 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Edelson, Morris, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Ellis, Royston, 1962 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Emails-Mixed, 1997-2009 (Box 42, Folder 9-10)
  - Erotics Gallery, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Fan Mail, 1960s-1970s (Box 50, Folder 1-10)
  - Farber, Seth, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Feral Faun, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Ferlinghetti, Lawrence, 1960-1971 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - FEVA (Federation of East Village Artists), 2003 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Fleming, Don, 2006-2007 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Foreign Publisher Correspondence/Contracts (Re: 1001 Ways to Make Love), 1966-1971 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Free University, 1965, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Freedom Press, 1969 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - The Fugs Fan Mail, 1966-1977 (Box 42, Folder 20, Box 50, Folder 11-12)
  - Gadfly Magazine, 1999, undated (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Georgakas, Dan (Re: Publish Kupferberg Works), 1977 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Gershow, Pete, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Ginsberg, Allen. Poems and Ginsberg Trust-Related, 1958-1960, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Ginzburg, Ralph (Re: Fact Magazine), 1967 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Ginzy: The Nation (Poems for the Nation), 1999 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Gitlin, Todd, 1969, undated (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Godden, William, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - Goldgar, Harry (Newsletter), 1992, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Goldstein, Al (Re: Submissions, Interview for Screw Magazine), 1970, 1979 (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Good, Fergus, 2004-2005 (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Goodman, Paul, 1958 (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - Graf, Robert, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - Greening, Thomas, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - Gwerder, Urban, 1989-2008 (Box 42, Folder 35-36)
  - Hachman, Tom, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 37)
  - Harpoon, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 38)
  - Hentoff, Nat, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 39)
  - Hershey, Solomon, 1967 (Box 42, Folder 40)
  - Higgins, Dick, 1960-1973 (Box 42, Folder 41)
  - Hodge, John, 2005-2008 (Box 42, Folder 42)
  - Hoffman, Abbie, 1971, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 43)
  - Holman, Bob, 1988, 2008 (Box 42, Folder 44)
  - Holstein, Neil (Re: Ruskin Documentary), 2000 (Box 42, Folder 45)
  - Hooton, Harry (Re: Works and Related), 1959-1961, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 46)
  - House, Tom, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 47)
  - Huxley, Aldous, 1960 (Box 257, Folder 27)
  - I'm Glad I Didn't Say That (Book), 1980-1982 (Box 42, Folder 48)
  - International Institute for Applied Systems Analysis (Re: Paper on Reevaluating the Value of Life), 1980 (Box 42, Folder 49)
  - IT Magazine, 1969 (Box 42, Folder 50)
  - Jakobsson, Robert, 1991-1996 (Box 42, Folder 51)
  - Joans, Ted, 1952-2002 (Box 42, Folder 52)
  - Johnson, Ray, 1958-1959, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 53)
  - Jola, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 54)
  - Jones, Baird (Re: Kupferberg Exhibit), 1987, 1996 (Box 42, Folder 55)
  - Jones, Dedwydd, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 56)
  - Jones, LeRoi (aka Amiri Baraka), 1958 (Box 42, Folder 57)
  - Kaiser, Chris, 1988 (Box 42, Folder 58)
  - Kaja, 1960 (Box 42, Folder 59)
  - Karl, Erwin, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 60)
  - Kaufman, Allen (Re: Outlaw Poets Book), circa 1999 (Box 42, Folder 61)
  - Kirby, David, 1979 (Box 42, Folder 62)
  - Kirk, J., 1967 (Box 42, Folder 63)
  - Kleinbeast, Devorah, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 64)
  - Kopit, Barbara, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 65)
  - Krakauer, Daniel, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 66)
  - Kramer, 1990-1991 (Box 42, Folder 67)
  - Krassner, Paul, 1963-2005 (Box 42, Folder 68)
  - Krech, Richard (The Fugs' Lawyer), 2003 (Box 42, Folder 69)
  - Krim, Seymour, 1960-1968 (Box 42, Folder 70)
  - Kutzman, Harvey, undated (Box 42, Folder 71)
  - The Last International, 1983 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Lederman, Robert and Alexander Cockburn, 1996-1997 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Legman, G., 1950-1967 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Leisner, Roger, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Less Newspoems (Re: Orders, Permissions), 1981-1982 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Letters To/From, 2006, undated (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Letters To/From Publishers & Editors and Performance Requests/Information, 1950-2007 (Box 43, Folder 6-13)
  - Levy, D.A., 1967 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Lewis, Jeff, 2004-2009 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Lindenberg, Kal, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Lini, Jonathan, 1996 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Listen to the Mockingbird (Third Edition), 1979-1981 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Literal Latte' (Re: Publication), 1998 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Lo Zibetto Exhibition, 1983-1984 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Lopez, Dennis, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Lowenfels, Walter, 1958-1964 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Mac Low, Jackson, 1949, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - MacArthur, John, 2008 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Macrae, Laurie, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Magic Bullet Press, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Mail Art, 1994-2004 (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Mailer, Norman, 1958-1985 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Martish, Tom, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - Mayhew, Fergus, 1992 (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - McCarthy, Tim, 1980-1994 (Box 43, Folder 31-32)
  - McDarrah, Fred (Re: Beat Generation Book), 1996 (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - McGinley, Desire, undated (Box 43, Folder 34)
  - McLuhan, Marshall, 1959, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 35)
  - Mekas, Adolphas/Jonas, 1967, 2001 (Box 43, Folder 36)
  - Miles (From Long Hair Magazine), 1965 (Box 43, Folder 37)
  - Miller, Henry, 1958-1975 (Box 43, Folder 38)
  - Miller, Tom, 1976-1977 (Box 43, Folder 39)
  - Mirabito, Shiv, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 40)
  - Miscellaneous Requests/Acceptance for Performances, Invitations, Submissions, 1968-2006 (Box 43, Folder 41)
  - Miscellaneous Mailings, 1993-2006 (Box 43, Folder 42)
  - Moore, Dudley, 1974 (Box 43, Folder 43)
  - Morland, Harold (aka Sam), 1960-1963 (Box 43, Folder 44)
  - Moscow Trials Campaign Committee, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Moyse, Arthur, 1962-1991 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - MPI Media-WPA Film Library (1960s CD-ROM), 1994-1995 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Nadeau, Mark, 1989 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Naropa Institute (Re: Allen Ginsberg Tribute), 1994 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - National Peace Officer Training Organization, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Neville, Richard, 1971, 2008 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - New York Press, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - New Yorker Rejections, 2005 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Nin, Anais, 1958-1960 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - O God Requests, Etc., 1979-1980 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - O'Neil, Kevin, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Ohliger, John, 1997-2002 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Oisteanu, Valery, 1991 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Ono, Yoko, 2005 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - The Other America... (Exhibit), 1983 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Other's Manuscripts, circa 1950s-1980s (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Owl Art Studio (Robin Tatham), 1997-2008 (Box 44, Folder 18-19)
  - P-Orridge, Genesis, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Paskal, Cleo, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Paskal, Tom, 1976, 2001 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Pastor, Andrea, 2000 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Pell, Derek (Re: Dingbat Publication), 1995 (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - The Penis Monologues, 2002 (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Perez, Rich, 2000-2001 (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - Petroff, Stephen, 1967-2007 (Box 44, Folder 27-29)
  - Plantenga, Bart, 2005 (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - The Poetry Project, 1984-2004 (Box 44, Folder 31)
  - Poets & Writers, Inc., 1988-1998 (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - Poland, Jefferson, 1983 (Box 44, Folder 33)
  - Pollet, Sylvester, 2006 (Box 44, Folder 34)
  - Publishing Correspondence (Re: Fucknam Play, Etc.), 1967-1970 (Box 44, Folder 35)
  - Questionable Cartoons-Related, 1980-1993 (Box 44, Folder 36)
  - Radical Humor (Re: Rejections, Etc.), 1959, 1979-1984 (Box 44, Folder 37-38)
  - Reich, William / Foundation (Re: Purchase and Use of Orgone Energy Accumulator, Newsletters, and Index), 1950-1957 (Box 44, Folder 39-40)
  - Reilly, J.N., 2005 (Box 44, Folder 41)
  - Reineke, Beth, 2005 (Box 44, Folder 42)
  - Rejection Letters, 1972-2006 (Box 44, Folder 43)
  - Requests/Thank You for Performances, 1966-1973 (Box 44, Folder 44)
  - Responses (to Kupferberg's Village Voice Personal Ad Re: Beautiful Woman), 1991 (Box 44, Folder 45)
  - Rethinking Marxism Journal, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 46)
  - Roskos, Dave (Includes Big Hammer Publication), 2003 (Box 44, Folder 47)
  - Royal Society of Leichtenstein, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 48)
  - Sacharoff, Mark, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Sanders, Ed, 1963-2010 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Scharf, Lee / La Roy, 1989-2009 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Scott, Robert (Re: Exciting Times, High Times), 1988 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Seeger, Pete, 2006-2008 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Sharp, Rebby, 1991-1993 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Singh, Rani (Harry Smith Archive), 2005 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Snyder, Gabriel (Re: New York Post Article), 2001 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - SoHo Weekly News Submission, undated (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Solidaridad Obrera, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Sonenschein, David, 1981 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Sparrow, 1992-1999, 2005 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Sports Research, 2000 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Sports Injury Research, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Stadtlichter Books, 2008 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Strausbaugh, John, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Submission/Acceptance Letters, 1957-1959 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Subscriptions (for Kupferberg Publications), 1978-1981 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Sutcliffe, Penny, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Swedish Correspondence (Re: Translation of 1001 Ways to Live Without Working), 2008 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Take Over (Publication), 1978 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Taylor, Steve, 2008 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Tentatively, A Convenience, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Timothy Leary Defense Fund, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Tired of Waiting Committee Newsletter, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - Tobias, Allen, 1966-1998, 2008-2009 (Box 45, Folder 26-27)
  - Topp, Sylvia, undated (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Torregian, Sotere, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - True Professions (Re: Requests for Book), 1980-1981 (Box 45, Folder 30)
  - Turner, Chris, 2005 (Box 45, Folder 31)
  - TV Nation/Michael Moore (Re: Kupferberg Notes for New Show), 1997-1998 (Box 45, Folder 32)
  - TV's Bloopers and Practical Jokes (Re: Consent for Use of Celebrity Images), 1985-1986 (Box 45, Folder 33)
  - Ungar, Sanford (Re: Mole Magazine), 1983 (Box 45, Folder 34)
  - Verlag Golem, 1988-1989 (Box 45, Folder 35)
  - Vidal, Gore (Letter to), undated (Box 45, Folder 36)
  - The Village Voice Submissions, 1996-1998 (Box 45, Folder 37)
  - Wagner, Gary, 1984-1989 (Box 45, Folder 38)
  - Wagner, Steve, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 39)
  - Waldman, Anne, 1986-1989 (Box 45, Folder 40)
  - Was It Good For Your Too? Requests, 1982-1984 (Box 45, Folder 41)
  - Weaver, Ken, 1969-2009 (Box 45, Folder 42)
  - Wehlau, Judith (Includes Artworks), 1965-1967 (Box 45, Folder 43-44, Box 326, Folder 4)
  - Weinstein, Ira, 1992 (Box 45, Folder 45)
  - Wilcock, John, 2007, undated (Box 45, Folder 46)
  - William, Michael, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 47)
  - Wilson, Peter, 2001-2007 (Box 45, Folder 48)
  - Wilson, Robert Anton, 1983-1986 (Box 45, Folder 49)
  - Winthrop, Nat, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 50)
  - Young, Izzy, 1990-1999 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - YouTube Mail, 2008 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Z., Bob (Re: Panic Button Press), 1992 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Zeitgeist Gallery, 1996 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Zelasnick (aka Zelasnic), Laura, 1982, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Zinn, Howard, 1995, 2006-2008 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - General (Re: Death), 1961-1999 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - General, 1950s (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - General, 1960s (Box 46, Folder 9-12)
  - General, 1970s (Box 46, Folder 13-16)
  - General, 1980s (Box 46, Folder 17-20, Box 47, Folder 1-5)
  - General, 1990s (Box 47, Folder 6-14)
  - General, 2000s (Box 48, Folder 1-11)
  - General, undated (Box 48, Folder 12-15)
- Series IX. Performance Props and Costumes, circa 1960s-2010; 25 Linear Feet in 1 manuscript box, 11 record cartons, 9 flat boxes, 1 oversize file folder, 1 oversize box, 2 musical instruments, 1 toy gun, 1 suitcase
  Materials in this series were grouped by the processing archivist into boxes by item type when possible.
  This series contains clothing, musical instruments, and toys used by Kupferberg in his performances with his band the Fugs, his performing group Revolting Theater, Revolting News television episodes, and solo performances. Army uniforms and helmets; flags; hats; small musical instruments; masks; novelty toys; toy soldiers; t-shirts with slogans; and toy weapons in this series date from the 1960s to 2010. Two of Kupferberg's handmade "erectorines" (a broomstick with hundreds of bottle caps nailed onto it), as well as a black suitcase he used to transport props to performances can also be found in this series.
  Items found too badly damaged or stained were deaccessioned by the processing archivist. Deaccessioned material includes bug-infested clothing, heavily stained t-shirts, rusted metal, melted candy, and broken, sharp objects.
  - Packaged Toys, circa 1960s-2010 (Box 291)
  - Costume Masks, circa 1960s-2010 (Box 292)
  - Toy Soldiers, Action Figures, circa 1960s-2010 (Box 293)
  - T-Shirts and Sweatshirt, circa 1960s-2010 (Box 294)
  - Fug and Kupferberg Cartoon T-Shirts, Sweatshirt, and Mug, circa 1960s-2010 (Box 295)
  - Clothing, circa 1960s-2010 (Box 330, Box 296)
  - Military Helmets and Hats, Baseball Caps, circa 1960s-2010 (Box 297)
  - Military Hats and Helmets, circa 1960s-2010 (Box 298)
  - Small Musical Instruments, circa 1960s-2010 (Box 299)
  - Military Gear and Toy Weapons, circa 1960s-2010 (Box 300, Box 290)
  - Cigarettes and Matchbooks, circa 1960s-2010 (Box 301)
  - Glasses Frames: Reading, Sun, Joke, circa 1960s-2010 (Box 302)
  - Military Jacket with Buttons, Pins, and Ribbons, circa 1960s-2010 (Box 303)
  - Black Suitcase with Clothing and Baby Doll, circa 1960s-2010; cuid8698 (Item mss.385.cuid8698)
  - Novelty Signs, Buttons (Fug and Political), circa 1960s-2010 (Box 305, Folder 1-3)
  - Erectorine (Musical Instrument), circa 1960s-2010; cuid8699 (Box 328, Item mss.385.cuid8699)
  - Erectorine (Musical Instrument), circa 1960s-2010; cuid8701 (Item mss.385.cuid8701)
  - Wooden Toy Gun, circa 1960s-2010; cuid8700 (Box 329, Item mss.385.cuid8700)
  - Ceramic figures, dolls, pens, necklaces, cake-toppers, yo-yos, balls, circa 1960s-2010 (Box 306, Box 307, Box 308, Box 319, Box 320, Box 321)
  - Candle, Dishes, Toys, Stuffed Animals, circa 1960s-2010 (Box 309)
  - Small Signs, Record Albums, Slides, Badges, circa 1960s-2010 (Box 310)
  - Signs, Paper Uncle Sam, circa 1960s-2010 (Box 40, Folder 10)